- Hey. - Hi.
- 嘿... - 嘿!
Phoebe, what's wrong?
菲比，出了什麼事嗎？
I'm just so exhausted from dragging around this huge engagement ring.
戴著這個超大訂婚戒指快要把我累死了！
- Oh, my God. - Congratulations.
-噢！天啊！ -恭喜你啊！哇！
So did he get on one knee? Did he have a speech prepared?
他有沒有跪下來？他有準備求婚詞嗎？
Oh, did he cry?
噢！他有哭嗎？
Yeah, big surprise, I like proposals.
沒錯，我喜歡求婚，很奇怪嗎？
Well, it was really sweet, and, like, the most romantic thing ever.
實在是很溫馨，是我人生中最浪漫的一刻。
Here's to Phoebe, who's found the greatest guy in the world.
嘿，我們來敬菲比 為了她找到世界上最好的男人乾一杯。
To Phoebe and..
敬菲比和...
I want to say "Mike"?
應該是麥克吧？
- To Phoebe and Mike. - Hey.
-敬菲比和麥克！ -喔！
Thank you. Oh, and I have something for you.
謝謝大家！ 噢，我有點東西要給你！
It's my little black book. It's got the numbers of all the guys I've dated.
這是我的小記事本 裡面有我約會過的男生的電話
Oh, Phoebe, that's nice, but you know what? I think I'm okay.
噢，菲比。很謝謝你，但我想我用不上了。
Give it to one of your other single girlfriends.
你還是把它送給你其他獨身的女性朋友吧
I would, but you're the last one.
我也想，但你是最後一個獨身的了
Give me the book!
那給我吧！
"Pablo Diaz.
巴布羅.迪亞斯
Brady Smith.
布裡迪.史密斯
Guy in Van"?
「開貨車的男生」
Oh, my first love.
那是我的初戀！
What is the red X next to Bob Gremore's name mean?
巴伯.格裡莫的名字旁邊標著個X是什麼意思？
Dead.
死掉了。
Oh, it's okay. No, he was old. Yeah.
沒關係，他已經很老了。
And he lived a full life. He was in the first wave at Omaha Beach.
他也活夠了，奧馬哈移民潮時他也在場。
I should've given you guys my black book when I got married.
嘿，對不起 我結婚時也應該把我的電話本給你們男生的。
Although, it wasn't so much a book as a napkin.
儘管那不算是電話本，只是一張皺皺的紙...
With Janice's phone number on it.
...上面寫著珍妮斯的電話。
Phoebe, isn't Jethro Tull a band?
菲比，Jethro Tull不是一個樂隊嗎？
Oh, yes, they are.
沒錯。
The One with Ross's Grant
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
Hey, honey.
嘿，老婆
Hey, sweetie.
嘿，老公
- Is Monica not here? - No.
-莫尼卡不在嗎？ -不在。
Then I'll tell you. My agency was bidding for a big account, and they got it.
那我先告訴你吧，我的經紀爭取到一個大廣告客戶
- It's my first national commercial. - Cool.
-這是我第一個跨國廣告 -酷！
And I don't want to brag, but a lot of the ideas were mine.
不是我吹牛，但很多內容都是我構思出來的！
Hell, you weren't there. All the ideas were mine.
拜託，你有沒有在聽啊？全部構思都是我的！
That's great. Hey, can you cast me in it?
太好了！嘿，可以介紹我去拍廣告嗎？
I really don't think you're right for the part.
...不知道啊，我想你不適合裡面的角色。
What do you mean? I can do anything. I'm a chameleon.
怎麼會？我可以演任何角色。我是一條變色龍呢！
I'm old.
我很老！
I'm tired.
我很累！
Oh, I am hot. I'm cold. Come on, what can't I do?
嘿！我很熱！我很冷！ 呵？？拜託，有什麼我不能演？
First of all, bravo.
我得說，精彩...
But I don't think you're right for this. The part's a stuffy college professor.
但我覺得你真的不適合 這個角色是一個死板的大學教授。
I can do that. Hello, I'm your professor.
也可以啊！ 你好，我是你們的教授。
When I'm not busy thinking of important things, or professing..
當我有空或者沒有...演講的時候
I like to use.. What's the product?
我會用...噢！是什麼產品？
Software that facilitates inter-business networking e-solutions.
電子商務網絡解決方案。
I'm cold.
我很冷！
- Hey. - Hey.
- 嘿! - 嘿!
Guess who's a finalist for a huge research grant?
猜猜誰有可能得到一筆龐大的科研補助金！
I'll give you a hint. He's looking right at you.
給你個提示，他正在看著你。
Well, unless it's the creepy guy with his hand up his kilt..
除非你說的是那個穿裙子的怪人
I'm gonna say, "Congratulations."
恭喜你！
I'm so excited. Apparently, I beat out hundreds of other applicants..
我實在是太興奮了，我擊敗了其他的幾百個競爭者
including five guys I went to graduate school with.
包括我們研究所的五個同事。
Not that I'm keeping score, or anything. Five.
不是我吹噓，但...五個人!
- Wow, that's great. - Yeah.
-哇!太厲害了。 - 是啊！
- So tell me about the grant. - Well, okay, it's for $25,000.
-那個是什麼補助金？ -那是25,000美元的補助
And if I get it, I'll be able to complete my field research.
如果我得到了 那我就可以完成我那領域的研究了。
And there will be an article about me in the Paleontology Review.
然後我就可以在「古生物學刊」裡發表我的論文了
It'll be the first time my name is in there..
那是我頭一次在那本書上發表論文
without people raising serious questions about my work.
而其他人不會懷疑
- Are you talking about the Dewer Grant? - Yeah. Why?
-等等，你是說杜瓦基金？ -沒錯，怎麼了？
Benjamin Hobart is administering that grant.
本傑明.哈伯特管理著那個基金
- Your ex-boyfriend? - Yeah.
-你的前任男朋友？ -對。
So your ex-boyfriend is gonna determine if your new boyfriend gets this grant?
那麼說 你的前男友決定了你現任男友是否能得到那筆錢？
Wow, your new boyfriend is screwed.
哇，你的現任男友真草包。
No. No, we ended on great terms.
沒有，我們很愉快的分手的。
If anything, I think this could help you. You know what?
我意思是，如果對你有幫助的話
Why don't we all go out to dinner, and I can introduce you.
我們可以把他約出來吃個飯啊 我可以把你介紹給他。
- If you think it'd help. - Yeah, absolutely. I'll call him.
-是嗎？你覺得有幫助嗎？ -當然啦，我給他打電話啦。
Now, is there anything I could do to butter him up?
那，我可以做什麼去...迎合他啊？
Anything he really likes?
他喜歡點什麼？
He does have a pretty serious latex fetish.
唔...他有一整套小玩偶。
We'll see how dinner goes.
我知道該怎麼做了。
- Hey. - Hey, you want to go see a movie?
- 嘿! - 嘿，想去看電影嗎？
I told you I had to spend all day clearing out stuff so Mike could move in.
我已經告訴過你我今天一整天要打掃 好讓麥克搬進來住。
- Oh, right. - Yeah.
- 噢！對哦. - 沒錯.
Now that I'm here, I might as well help with the cleaning and organizing.
既然我都來了，我就幫你清潔和收拾一下吧！
I just happen to have my label maker.
剛好我有打標籤機
Oh, it's so hard to get rid of stuff.
噢，要丟棄自己的物品太難了！
Did you and Chandler make compromises when you moved in together?
你和錢德要同居的時候 有為丟棄東西煩惱過嗎？
Chandler did.
錢德有煩惱過！
- What does he want you to give up? - A bunch of stuff.
-他想你丟棄什麼？ -很多東西啊
And the worst one, he wants me to get rid of Gladys.
我最捨不得的是...他要我丟掉格拉達斯。
Who's Gladys?
誰是格拉達斯？
What a tragic loss.
噢！多麼可怕的浪費啊！
Yeah, I really hate to give her up. Oh, I know. Oh, you should take her.
就是說。我真的不想放棄她啊。 噢！我想到了，你可以帶她走啊！
I don't know.
這個，我..我也不知道好不好...
- What, you don't like her? - Of course I do. What's not to like?
-為什麼？你不喜歡她嗎？ -我當然喜歡她啊。有什麼好不喜歡的！
I'd take her in a minute.
我可以馬上就把她拿走！
But I think that you're giving up too easy.
但我覺得你現在說放棄太早了。
Honey, I think that you need to fight for her.
我想你應該為她作鬥爭！
- Really, you think? - Absolutely.
-你覺得是這樣嗎？ -當然啦！
You say to him, "I'm sorry, Mike, I can't live without her.
你對他說: 對不起，麥克。 我不能失去她
She means too much to me."
她對我來說很重要
Okay, I'll fight for her. Okay.
好的，我是該為她爭取一下。
Oh, wait. I just realized, if I do that, that means you don't get her.
等等，我忽然想到... 如果我這樣做，你就無法得到她了。
Damn it, I did not think this through.
對哦，怎麼我沒想到呢！
Emma, mom's got a snack for you.
艾瑪, 媽媽給你做了小吃
You know, every now and then, she might like some barbecue potato chips.
你知道 她有時喜歡些烤肉味的番茄薯片
- Hey, guys. - Hey.
-嘿，你們。 -嘿
- Hi. - Hey, baby.
-嘿 -嘿, 寶貝
Oh, any word on casting yet?
你給我的推薦有回復了嗎？
- I told you, you're not right for the part. - What do you mean?
-喬伊，我已經說過了，你不適合那個角色。 -什麼意思啊？
Rach, don't I seem like a professor you'd buy some kind of e-crap from?
瑞秋，你會不會花錢 買像我這樣的教授介紹的電子貨啊？
I'm sorry, this sounds like something I'm never gonna be interested in.
不好意思，我對這種東西沒什麼興趣。
Look, come on, please? It's not like I'm asking you for some crazy favor.
拜託啦！好像我很為難你似的。
This is what I do for a living. I am a professional actor.
這是我的工作啊，我是個職業的演員呢！
Man, I'm two hours late for work.
噢！原來我遲到兩個小時了！
Here's my reel. It's got all the commercials that I've been in.
這裡有我的一盤磁帶，裡面有我拍過的所有廣告。
- Joe.. - Just watch it.
-喬伊... -你就看一下吧
If you don't like it, don't pass it on to your bosses.
如果你不喜歡就別給你上司就是了。
- Fine. - Thank you.
-好吧！ -謝謝。
- Work, Joe. - Damn it.
-工作啦，喬伊！ -可惡！
- What am I gonna do now? - Just pass the tape along.
-我該怎麼辦啦？ -就給你上司看看咯！
He's not right for the part.
他的確不適合演這個。
If I suggest him, my bosses will think I'm an idiot.
如果我推薦他 我的老闆會發現我是個傻瓜！
And that's something they should learn on their own.
我希望我的老闆能遲些才發現這一點
Just tell Joey that you watched the tape..
那就告訴喬伊你看過帶子
and you liked it, but your bosses didn't.
你很喜歡 但你的老闆們不喜歡。
Then you're the good guy, and they're the bad guy.
那樣，你就成了好人，壞人就是你的老闆啦。
That's good. I liked it, they didn't.
好主意！我喜歡，老闆不喜歡。
Joey, for God's sake, go to work.
喬伊，看在上帝份上，去工作啦！
I can't believe I'm about to meet Benjamin Hobart.
無法相信我能見到本傑明.哈伯特。
I've always thought of him as someone I'd invite..
我一直以為
to my fantasy dinner party.
只有在夢中才能和他共聚晚餐呢
Do you think there's any chance he'll bring Christie Brinkley or C-3PO?
他會不會帶上一些他喜歡的小玩偶來呢？
Sorry, it looks like it's just him.
對不起，看來他只孤身一人。
Charlie.
查莉！
My God, you look absolutely stunning.
天啊，你簡直美得讓我頭暈了。
Well, I am having a good hair day.
是嗎？今天我特地去了理髮。
- It's so good to see you. - Oh, you too.
- 見到你真好。 - 我也是。
I'm okay.
我沒事。
I'm sorry. Ross Geller, Benjamin Hobart.
對不起...羅斯.蓋勒 本傑明.哈伯特
It's an honor to meet you. I can't tell you how long..
很榮幸見到你。 我仰慕你都不知道多久了
I've been an admirer of your work. I mean, that Nobel Prize.
我是說，你得的諾貝爾獎，喔！
I mean, I have to tell you that you're one of the reasons I got into the field.
我得說 你是我從事科學工作的其中一個原因。
Well, likewise.
噢，是嗎，我也是。
Not likewise. I'd never heard of you until this morning.
其實，不一樣，我今早才第一次聽到你的名字。
But it's nice to be nice.
但，很高興能見到你。
- Shall we? - Yeah. Thank you.
- 我們...？ - 好的！
I can't believe that you chose this restaurant.
不能相信你選了這個餐館！
- Do you remember the night? - Oh, my God. I completely forgot.
-你還記得那天晚上嗎？ -噢 天啊，我都已經想不起了！
Oh, my God, I can't believe they let us back in this place.
天啊，我們居然又在這裡碰頭了！
You weren't there.
你當時不在場！
No, but, you know, it's just a funny image.
是不在，但想想都好笑
You know, the two of you in this restaurant with the..
想想你們兩個 在這個餐館，還...
Ross, why don't you tell Benji about your proposal while I go to the ladies' room.
羅斯 我去洗手間的時候你能告訴本你的方案嗎？
So tell me about it.
來吧，告訴我吧。
Okay. Well, I would like to do a dig in the Painted Desert.
我們會在沙漠裡進行挖掘.
There are still several areas that haven't been fully excavated.
因為裡面還有些地區還沒完全開挖的。
- Break up with Charlie. - What?
-和查莉分手吧！ -什麼？
What?
什麼？
Did you just say, "Break up with Charlie"?
你剛才說 「和查莉分手」嗎？
Well, yes and no. Yes, I did say it. And no, I didn't not say it.
可以說是，也可以說不是 是，我是這樣說了；不是，是我沒有否認。
- Kind of inappropriate, don't you think? - Listen, I'm sorry.
-你不應該這樣說的，是嗎？ -對不起。
I just haven't seen her for so long, all these feelings are rushing back.
因為我太久沒有見她了！ 以前的感覺又湧上心頭！
I'm starting to realize how much I've missed her.
我覺得又喜歡上她了
And I'm gonna need you to break up with her.
所以我想你和她分手
- Are you serious? - If you say, yes, then I'm serious.
-你是說真的嗎？ -如果你說是，那我就是認真的
If you say, no, then I'm joking.
如果你說不是，那我就是開玩笑！
- No. - Joking it is.
-不是！ -我開玩笑的！
- Hi, sorry I'm late. - Hey, how'd it go with Mike?
-嗨！對不起，我遲到了。 -嘿，和麥克談得怎樣？
- Is he gonna let you keep the painting? - No, he really hates it.
-他肯讓你保留那幅畫嗎？ -不行，他實在很討厭它
But he's gonna let me keep my box of human hair.
但他肯讓我留下我那盒頭髮！
So you gotta pick your battles. But the good news is, Gladys is yours.
所以我只能妥協了。 但好消息是，格拉達斯已經屬於你了！
Wow, what's the bad news?
哇，那壞消息呢！？
- Who's Gladys? - Oh, she's that work of art I made.
-誰是格拉達斯？ -噢！她是我的手工作品，你見過啦
You know, with the woman coming out of the frame.
就是有個女人從畫裡面走出來的那幅畫啊
And Monica gets to keep her?
噢，莫尼卡把她收下了嗎？
In her house? I am so jealous.
放在這個房間裡？我要嫉妒了！
I didn't know you wanted her too.
噢！我不知道你也想要她啊！
Well, I mean, sure, of course.
我..當然想要啊。
But you already gave that to Monica, so..
但..你已經給了莫尼卡了，所以...
- You know, I would give her up for you. - No, I couldn't let you do that.
-為了你，我可以放棄她。 -不行，我不可以讓你這樣做的。
- No, but I want to. - But I don't want you to.
-但我想這樣做。 -但我不想你這樣做。
- But I insist. - But I insist harder.
-但我堅持！ -但我更堅持！
Girls. Girls. Stop. Okay, we'll flip a coin.
女生們！停一停好嗎？我們投硬幣決定吧。
Heads, she's Rachel's. Tails, she's Monica's.
正面，她是瑞秋的 反面，她就是莫尼卡的。
- Tails. Monica, she's yours. - No, that landed in your food.
-反面！莫尼卡，她是你的了！ -不行，它掉到你的食物裡了
No, no, that's okay. You won fair and square. I'm so sad.
不，沒關係，該贏的就該贏。我太難過了。
Then the little red squirrel took all of his acorns..
然後紅色的小松鼠把他所有的橡子(果實)
and put them in his little satchel and set off for..
放進他的小背包裡, 離開了
Okay. Someone's getting a little fussy. I think it's time for bed.
好啦!有人開始煩啦 我看該睡覺了
Where's the little red squirrel going?
小松鼠去哪了?
Hey, Joe?
嘿 喬伊！
Oh, that's so sweet.
哦，太好了
- What's up? - Bad news.
-什麼事？ -壞消息
I watched the tape and passed it along to my bosses and they weren't interested.
我看過了帶子並把它交給我的老闆們 但他們不感興趣。
I'm sorry, man.
對不起，老兄。
- But you watched the tape? - Yeah, I liked it.
-但...你看過這帶子嗎？ -是啊，我...我很喜歡啊！
But my bosses didn't go for it. Stupid sons of bitches.
但...我的老闆不喜歡。真他媽的可惡！
- You didn't watch the tape. - What? Of course I did.
-你沒有看過這帶子。 -什麼！？我當然看啦！
Look, it's one thing not to cast me, but to lie to me?
你不推薦我是一回事，但你對我說謊？
- I'm not lying to you. I watched it. - You lied again.
-我沒有說謊啊，我看了啦！ -你看，又說謊！
- I watched it. - Keep going, Pinocchio.
-我看了！ -繼續說謊吧，匹諾曹！
- I did. - No, you didn't.
-我看了！ -沒有！ 你沒看！
I'm telling you, I watched the tape.
我告訴你，我看了這帶子。
- Did you watch the tape? - No.
-你看過這帶子嗎？ -沒有
Hi. Look, I realize only one of us can get this grant.
嗨, 聽著, 我知道我們中 只有一個人能得到認可
And I just wanted to wish both of you the best of luck.
而我也想祝福你們所有人好運
Are you crossing your fingers?
你繞手指了?
What, this? No. This.. That's just the result of a childhood injury.
什麼?這個?不, 這個... 只是童年受傷的結果
I'm cured!
治好了！
Good morning, everybody.
大家早上好
If you go ahead and take your seats we can get started.
如果你坐到座位上 我們就可以開始了
Actually, Dr. Hobart, can I have a word with you?
實際上，哈伯特博士 我能和你說句話嗎?
And you are?
你是...?
- Ross. - I know. I'm kidding.
- 羅斯 - 我知道, 開玩笑的
Listen, I just want to say, last night..
我只想說, 昨晚...
Dinner was a little awkward.
晚餐不太好
- I just wanna make sure we're okay. - Oh, yeah. Absolutely.
-我只想知道我們之間沒什麼問題 -沒問題!絕對沒有!
- You didn't tell Charlie what I said, did you? - Oh, no. Of course not.
- 你沒有告訴查莉我說過什麼吧? - 喔, 沒有, 當然沒有
Well, thank you. I want you to know, I respect your decision not to give her up.
謝謝你, 我想讓你知道我尊重你 沒有放棄她的決定
It was the biggest mistake I ever made in my whole life.
放棄她, 是我一生中最大的錯誤
Well, that and tattooing her name on my shoulder..
呃, 除了這件事 還有我很蠢的把她的名字刺在肩膀上...
last night stupidly.
昨天晚上犯的蠢..
Seriously?
真的?
My Nobel Prize was not for moving on.
我的諾貝爾獎可不是為了繼續談論..
- So no hard feelings? - None at all. Good luck today.
- 還難過嗎？ - 一點也沒有, 祝今天好運!
- Thank you. - Okay.
- 謝謝 - 不客氣
All right. The selection committee has chosen the three of you as our finalists.
評選委員會選出你們三人於今天作最後評核。
The ultimate decision will be based on the answers you give to the questions I ask.
最終決定會基於你們如何回答我的問題。
We're gonna go ahead and start with Dr. Li.
先從李博士開始吧。
You claim the field is too reliant on the Linnaean taxonomic system.
李博士 你提出學界太依賴林奈分類系統。
How do you propose to correct this problem?
那你打算怎麼解決這個問題？
Well, I believe that the answers lie in the osteological evidence.
我相信解決辦法在化石證據上
- I plan to begin there. - Interesting.
-我打算從那裡入手 -很有趣
I guess.
是嗎？
Dr. Biely, your proposal includes some fieldwork. Where might that take place?
白莉博士，你的方案有一些挖掘工作 你會從哪裡入手呢？
Primarily in the Pierre Shale region of South Dakota.
首先是南達科他州的Pierre Shale地區。
Certainly. Very well. And Dr. Geller, when is my birthday?
當然，很好。那蓋勒博士 你知道我的生日是什麼時候嗎？
What? I..
什麼？我...我...
Care to venture a guess?
不能猜一下嗎？
- May 12? - That's not even kind of close.
-5月12號？ -還差很遠呢！
Dr. Li, how many graduate students will you need?
李博士，你需要要多少個學生呢？
- Half a dozen. - I see. And Dr. Biely?
- 6個 -明白了，那白莉博士呢？
Three for excavation, and two for analysis.
三個負責開掘，兩個負責分析。
Certainly. Dr. Geller, which 1965 Shirelles hit..
當然。蓋勒博士，1965年沙倫斯樂隊
was later covered by a popular British Invasion band?
被哪支英國樂隊蓋過風頭？
What? I need six graduate students.
什麼...？我需要6個學生。
No, I'm sorry. We were looking for "Baby It's You."
不是！對不起 答案是 「Baby It's You」（寶貝，就是你）
"Baby It's You."
寶貝，就是你。
What? Wait just a minute.
什麼...？等等，等一下。
None of my questions have anything to do with paleontology.
我的問題沒有一條是關於古生物學的。
You're right, I apologize. Scratch the last question.
沒錯，我該道歉。 那最後一條問題
Spell "Boscodictiasaur."
拼寫單詞Boscodictiasaur。
I've never heard of a "Boscodictiasaur."
恩....我沒有聽過Boscodictiasaur啊。
Yeah, I just made it up. Spell it.
是，我亂編的單詞。快拼。
- Okay. B-O.. - No, it starts with a silent M.
-好的。B - O - S ... -不，開頭有個不發音的「M」。
Oh, come on!
噢，拜託！
I can't believe Joey. I hate being called a liar.
我不明白喬伊，我討厭被人稱為騙子。
But you are a liar.
但你是個騙子。
What did I just say?
我剛剛怎麼說的？
- Are you still here? - Yes.
-你還在啊？ -是的，而且我還有話說
And I'm not just hurt, I'm insulted. When I tell somebody I did something..
我不僅僅是受傷害，我感覺被侮辱了一樣。 當我說我已經做了某事...
Okay, hold on, let me just stop you right there, okay? First, you lied. Right?
好了好了... 我打斷你一下好嗎？ 首先，你說謊，對嗎？
Then you lied about lying, okay?
然後，你又說謊去圓謊，好嗎？
Then you lied about lying about lying, okay?
然後，你又再說謊去圓你剛才圓的謊 是不是？
So before you lie about lying about lying about lying about lying..
所以在你說謊去圓你剛才 為圓謊...而說的謊...的那個謊言...
Stop lying.
不要說謊啦！
Why are you so sure I didn't watch this tape?
為什麼你這麼肯定我沒有看過那帶子？
You wanna know why? You wanna know why?
你想知道...? 你想知道為什麼？
Well, this is going well.
事情發展得不錯呢。
Here's how I know you didn't watch.
這就是我知道你沒看的原因了。
If you had seen what was on this tape, believe me, you'd have some comments.
如果你看了這帶子，你絕對不會沒有話說的。
All right, remember, I got paid a lot of money for this..
聽好，我收了很多錢才去拍這個廣告
and it only aired in Japan.
而且只在日本地區放映。
Ichiban.
一級棒
Ichiban, lipstick for men.
男用唇膏！
And that's how I know you didn't watch the tape.
這就是我知道你沒看的原因！
He really is a chameleon.
他真的是一條變色龍呢。
Well, Gladys, say hello to your new home.
格拉達斯，給你的新家打個招呼吧！
- Oh, my. - Wow.
-我的...！ -哇！
Oh, she is so nice and big.
噢！她真漂亮，又顯眼！
Oh, Monica, where are you going to display Gladys, oh, so proudly?
噢！莫尼卡，你會把她放到什麼地方 讓格拉達斯顯的得體呢？
- I haven't really settled on a spot yet. - How about right above the TV?
-我還沒決定放在哪裡！ -那，不如放在電視機上面吧！
That way, it will be the first thing that you see when you walk in the door.
這樣的話，人們一進門就馬上看得到了！
Yeah, yeah, and you can get rid of that French poster.
好啊，好啊！那你就可以丟掉那法國的海報了。
- I like that poster. - Really?
-我喜歡那海報啊！ -是嗎？
It doesn't have anything coming out of it.
它沒有東西可以「冒」出來啊。
Or maybe there's someplace for her in your bedroom?
又或者你的臥室裡有空位嗎？
- There's nothing above your bed. - Are you still here?
-噢！你床頭還空著呢！ -你還在這裡住嗎？
Stupid Nobel Prize winner.
愚蠢的諾貝爾獎獲得者！
Oh, hi. Hello.
噢！嗨！你好！
Have you come to ask me some more paleontology-related questions?
呃，你是來問我古生物學的問題的嗎？
Your grandmother's nickname, perhaps? Ann-Margret's pant size?
呃...可能你要問我你祖母的小名吧？ 還是你馬格莉特阿姨內褲的尺寸？
I've come here to apologize. I think I may have let my feelings..
我是來道歉的。 我想我對查莉的感情…
for Charlie interfere with the interview process.
影響到面試的程序了
No. Stop.
沒有！哪裡有！
Anyway, I decided to offer you the grant.
不管怎麼說，我決定批准你的補助金。
- Really? - There is just one small stipulation.
-真的嗎？ -是的...只是還有一個...條件...
- I have to break up with Charlie? - Hey, you got one right.
-我要和查莉分手？ -嘿！你終於答對一次了！
- You're crazy. - Crazy or romantic?
-你發神經。 -神經，還是...浪漫？
Crazy.
神經！
- Or? - Get out!
-還是... -出去！
Oh, my God.
噢！天啊！
- What? - Joey, what is this thing doing here?
-什麼？ -喬伊，這..這...東西在這裡幹嘛？
I got her from Monica. She sold it to me for a very reasonable price.
我在莫尼卡那裡拿過來的 她出了個很合理的價格。
- Joey, we're not keeping this. - But it's an original Buffay.
-喬伊，我們不能留著這個！ -但它是原版的布費作品啊...
All right, fine. You can keep it.
好的，沒關係，你就留著吧。
As long as you don't mind that she's haunted.
只要你不介意她周圍遊蕩。
Hey, what? What?
嘿？什麼？什麼？嘿！噢！什麼！？
Well, legend has it, Joey, that she comes alive when you're asleep.
有這樣一個傳說...她在半夜裡會活過來。
She climbs out of the frame..
她爬出這畫框
and then drags her half-a-body across the floor..
然後她拖著她這半個身體，爬在地板上
just looking for legs to steal.
想辦法去偷一雙腿
And then with her one good hand..
然後她用她唯一的一隻手
she slowly reaches up..
慢慢、慢慢地
and turns your doorknob.
扭開門把手
Get that legless witch out of here!
拿走這沒腳的妖怪！！
- Hey, I sold that to Joey. - Yeah, well, I told him it's haunted.
-嘿！我把它賣給喬伊了！ -所以我騙他這是鬼怪了
- Two can play at this game. - Too late. You can't give it back.
-我們都會玩這種把戲 -不行，太遲了，你不能退貨！
- Oh, yes, I can. - No, you can't, she's yours.
-我當然可以！ -不，你不可以，她是你的 ！
- She's yours. - She's yours.
-她是你的！ -是你的！
- She's yours. - Hey.
-她是你的！ -嘿！
- She's mine. - She's mine.
-她是我的！ -是我--的！
-她是我的！ -她是我的！
You guys, you don't have to fight over her anymore.
你們啊！不用為她爭吵了。
Whoever doesn't get Gladys, gets Glynnis.
誰得不到格拉達斯，就把格林妮斯拿回去吧。
- I want Gladys. - She's mine.
-我要格拉達斯。 -她是我的！
- She's mine. - She's mine.
-她是我的！ -她是我的！
No, no. You don't get to do that.
不要不要.你們不要這樣了
I know. Look, I'm sorry I didn't give them your tape.
很抱歉我沒有把你的帶子給他們。
And I promise next time to submit you, whether I think you're right or not.
我保證，下次無論合不合適我都會把你推薦上去的。
That's not the point, Chandler. The point is that you lied.
重點不是這個啊錢德。 重點是，你說了謊
I know. You're right. What's it gonna take for you to forgive me?
我知道，你說的對 我要做什麼你才能原諒我？
Oh, my God.
噢 天啊！
Excellent.
無得彈！
Now what do you say?
現在你該說什麼？
Lying is wrong.
說謊是不對的！
And? And?
還有呢？...還有呢？
I'm a pretty little girl.
我是個漂亮美眉。
I knew it.
我早就知道啦！
Your ex-boyfriend is insane.
你的前男友是個瘋子。
- He is a character. - No, no, no.
-他是個有個性的人 -不是, 才不是呢
Charles Nelson Reilly is a character.
查爾斯·納爾遜·賴利才是
- Who? - Charles Nelson Reilly.
- 誰? - 查爾斯·納爾遜·賴利
The Ghost and Mrs. Muir? Match Game?
The Ghost and Mrs. Muir? Match Game?（兩個電影名）
Were you never sick as a child?
你小時侯都沒得過病嗎?
- Whatever. Did you get the grant? - No. And you wanna know why?
- 隨便啦！ 你得到那筆補助了嗎？ - 沒有，你想知道為什麼嗎？
Because your ex-boyfriend is still in love with you.
因為你的前男友還是愛著你。
- What? - Yeah.
-什麼？ -沒錯
He refused me because I wouldn't give you up.
他沒有給我那筆補助，就因為我沒有放棄你。
Benji isn't in love with me. I mean, he broke up with me.
本不會還愛著我的。 因為當時是他拋棄我
- And besides, he's a very ethical man. - Really?
-而且，他是個認真的人。 -是嗎？？？
Is it ethical to ask someone in a grant review:
在補助調查中問這種問題：
"Who was the voice of Underdog?"
「誰是Underdog（電影名）的配音員？」  很認真嗎？
I'm sure he was just joking.
我肯定他是在開玩笑，羅斯。
If you don't believe me, let's go talk to him.
如果你不相信我，我們去找他對質吧。
I'm telling you, he didn't ask me one paleontological question.
可以告訴你 他沒有問過我一個關於考古學的問題
- Seriously? - Oh, I'm sorry. No, he did ask me one:
-真的嗎？ -哦，不是，他問了我一個。
"How do you spell Boscodictiasaur?"
呃...怎麼拼Mboscodictiosaur
Well, if it's like the Lake Mbosco in Congo, then M-B-O..
和剛果的Mbosco湖拼法一樣，那是M-B-O...
Damn it.
可惡！
Dr. Geller. Charlie, what are you doing here?
蓋勒博士...？查莉  你...你到這來幹什麼？
I want you to tell her everything.
我要你告訴他一切。
About the deal you tried to make with me, about the crazy questions you..
告訴他你想和我做的交易，那些神經病的問題
Wally Cox. That's the voice of Underdog.
沃利·考克斯！他就是Underdog的配音！
Like I tried to tell you in the interview..
就如之前的調查我告訴你一樣
this grant is not based on your knowledge of pretty useless trivia.
這個補助基金不是為了這些無聊的知識而設的
No, don't do that. I want you to look her in the eyes and tell her the truth.
不！不！不！別這樣！ 我要你看著她的眼睛，告訴她真相。
Benji?
All right. It's true. I behaved horribly, but it's only because I still love you.
是的，的確是這樣。我之前簡直是亂來。 但這都是因為我還愛著你。
And I would do anything to have you back in my life.
只要你回到我身邊，我可以做任何事。
Too little, too late, Benji.
太少了，太遲了，Benji！
- I can't believe this. - I never should've broken up with you.
-我不敢相信。 -我真不應該離開你
I think about you all the time. Do you ever still think about me?
我無時無刻不想起你。 難道你一點都沒有想起我?
No.
沒有!
- Yes. - What?
-有! -什麼?
I don't know what to say, Benji. This is all so..
我不知道該說什麼好了，Benji。 這一切實在太...
romantic.
浪漫了
Or?
或者...
I know I may be way out of bounds here..
我知道，或者我做得太過火了
but is there any chance you would take me back?
但我們還有機會在一起嗎？
Maybe.
或者可以...
Sweetie, this conversation is starting to make me a little uncomfortable.
甜心，你們的對話讓我覺得有點不舒服了。
Oh, God. I am so sorry, but..
噢 天啊！我很抱歉，但...
I mean, there's so much history between us, you know?
我是說...我們之前有太多的過去了...
I'm sorry too.
我也覺得抱歉...
- I love you. - I love you too.
-我愛你! -噢! 我也愛你!
Okay, that's it, we are seeing other people.
好了, 夠了。我們算是完了！
Gladys?
格拉達斯?
For the third time this week. Man, this does not get old.
哈哈哈，這個星期的第三次了。 老兄，你怎麼還沒長大啊？
- You're mean! - Oh, don't be such a baby. Please.
-你真可惡！ -不要這麼孩子氣啦！